elocalz.com 2012-04-23

# eLocalz

## Privacy Policy

**Why We Collect Personal Information**  
eLocalz.com collects personal information to personalize your experience with our site. The more we know about you, the more we can present you with information and features that will interest you. The facts you provide, along with data stored in your personal "cookie," (see below) may also be used to make your online experience faster and more convenient.

We also use user information to measure our success and performance. For example, aggregate information gives us an idea of the number of visitors we attract and how they navigate they site. The information we collect enables us to contact users with offers and advertisements that may appeal to them. At times, we may also use the information we collect to notify members of site updates and to promote special events at eLocalz.com.

**How We Gather Data on eLocalz.com Users**  
We gather information in a number of ways, depending on the section of our site you are using. If you are an advertiser and join our services, we may ask you for contact information. This information is used for account management purposes so we can better suit your needs. Your personal information will never be gathered without your knowledge or understanding.

When you visit our site, we collect may track this information through the use of a "cookie" or other technological means. This information is mainly used to keep track of the number of visitors that come to the site so we can better assist our advertisers.

Wherever we ask you for personal information, we try to include a link to this Privacy Policy for your review.

**Other Companies' Access to Your Personal Information**  
eLocalz.com does not sell, rent or trade user information to other companies. Our site may link to advertisers and sites that collect personally identifiable information about you when you access them from eLocalz.com. This type of collection or use of personal information is beyond eLocalz.com's control and is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

We may occasionally need to share your information with business partners who co-sponsor contests or other services. In these cases, we will provide only the data that is needed to make the service or contest successful. If we plan to share this type of information, we will notify you before we collect it. If you do not want eLocalz.com to share your information, simply choose not to allow the transfer by not using or signing up for the contest or service in question.

When you sign up to receive promotional items from us, we may need to share some personal information with the third parties helping us to complete your transaction or send you the items you have requested. When we share your information with such third parties, we will disclose only the information needed to complete your transaction. You will be informed at the time of registering that the information gathered may be sent to third parties.

**"Cookies" and Their Use at eLocalz.com**  
"Cookies" are small data files that are sent from the site to your browser and are stored on your hard drive, keeping track of your general activity on the site. When you make subsequent visits to the site, your cookie gives us a summary of your preferences and past experiences on the site. This allows us to tailor eLocalz.com to your needs.

Your cookie may be altered at different times throughout your visits to eLocalz.com, and it is updated frequently as you use various eLocalz.com features. Every time you enter eLocalz.com, our server may deliver certain customized information to you based on the data stored in your cookie.

Some advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may use their own cookies. Again, these cases are beyond our control and are not included in eLocalz.com's Privacy Policy.

**Security**  
eLocalz.com stores all data behind carefully selected security devices, such as firewalls or offline computer equipment. All internal communication with the system and communication of private member data, such as credit card information, is transmitted using encrypted protocols. Policies related to staff access to private member data are in place. All data is held in the strictest confidence, protected by the strictest security standards.

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

**Your Agreement to This Privacy Policy**  
By using eLocalz.com, you indicate that you agree to the collection and use of your personal information by eLocalz.com as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Be sure to visit this page occasionally to find any updates we have made. We are committed to post Privacy Policy changes on this page so consumers can be sure of how eLocalz.com is gathering and using information about them.
